I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother George.
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig.
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Grandpa Pig is taking
Peppa and George on a boat trip.
Polly Parrot is going, too.
[squawks]
Grandpa Pig.
Have you got your mobile phone?
Yes, Granny Pig.
Don't drop it in the water.
No, Granny Pig.
Is it switched on?
Yes, Granny Pig.
Bye.
-Bye-bye.
[narrator] Here is Granddad Dog.
Ahoy there.
Ruff. Ahoy there.
Lovely day to go sailing.
I would go, too,
but my boat needs a clean.
[laughs]
I'm don't know why you bother cleaning
that rusty boat.
I'm surprised it's still afloat.
This rusty boat will still be afloat
long after your old tin boat has sunk
to the bottom of the river.
[barking and oinking]
[narrator] Granddad Dog
is Grandpa Pig's very best friend.
Full steam ahead. Goodbye.
I am the captain of this boat,
and when the captain tells you
to do something, you must do it.
[both] Aye, aye, captain.
Aye, aye, captain.
[kids laughing]
[narrator] Polly Parrot copies everything
that is said.
George, raise the flag.
[laughs]
Peppa, ring the bell.
Grandpa, can I be the captain? Please.
Okay, but as captain,
you must wear this hat.
[narrator] Now Peppa is the captain
and everyone must do what she says.
Ding the bell.
Turn that wheel.
Aye, aye, Captain Peppa.
Jump up and down.
[narrator] Captain Peppa is a bit bossy.
Perhaps I should be the captain again.
We don't want to crash into anything.
Steering the boat can be tricky.
Luckily, I'm good at steering.
[all gasp]
[narrator] Oh, dear. Grandpa Pig's boat
has crashed into a little island.
Grandpa, we're stuck.
I'll ring Granny Pig. She can get help.
[squawks]
[shouts]
[narrator] Grandpa Pig has dropped
his phone in the water.
[ringing]
Granny Pig speaking. Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Somehow, we need to get a message
to Granny.
Message to Granny.
Polly can fly to Granny.
Good idea, Peppa.
And I can teach Polly what to say.
Grandpa Pig says--
"Grandpa Pig says--"
--help, help.
--"help, help."
There you see. Easy peasy.
Grandpa Pig says, "Easy peasy."
You silly old bird.
Hello, Polly. What are you doing here?
[squawks]
Grandpa Pig says...
What does Grandpa Pig say?
-"You silly old bird.
-Oh!
Help. Help."
Goodness me. Grandpa must need help.
Granddad Dog.
Hello, Granny Pig.
Grandpa Pig needs help.
Please, could you rescue him?
Madame, I would be delighted.
[horn blows]
-Hooray.
Ahoy there. Do you need rescuing, captain?
Um, maybe.
Would you like my rusty old boat
to rescue you?
Yes, please, Granddad Dog.
Catch this, captain.
Aye, aye, skipper.
[narrator] Granddad Dog
is Grandpa Pig's very best friend.
Granny, did Polly tell you we needed help?
Yes. Polly is a very clever parrot.
Say, "I'm a clever parrot."
[barking]
"I'm a clever parrot."
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[phone ringing]
Hello. Daddy Pig speaking.
[person speaking in French]
Oh. Something's wrong with the phone.
You see? The phone's talking nonsense.
Hello?
[both speaking in French]
[in English] That was Monsieur Donkey.
He was speaking French.
Ha! I thought as much.
Mommy, what did Monsieur Donkey say?
He asked if little Delphine Donkey
could visit us.
Oh, goody.
[narrator] Delphine Donkey
is Peppa's very special friend
from France.
Delphine's coming
to practice talking English with us.
-Hooray.
We'd better hurry, Delphine's train
is arriving any minute.
Last stop. All change.
[Peppa] That's Delphine's train.
Delphine.
[speaks in French]
[narrator] Bonjour means hello in French.
[both speak in French then laugh]
Bonjour, Mr. Donkey.
My goodness.
Is that huge case for Delphine?
Yes. Delphine has brought
a few little things for her visit,
things you do not have over here,
cheese, bread, tomatoes, water.
Au revoir, Delphine.
I will pick you up tomorrow night.
Where shall I put Delphine's luggage?
In my room. At the very top of the house.
Oh.
And this luggage
is for one night's stay?
Oh, yes. That is why
I only pack a little bag.
[grunts]
Now, Delphine is here to practice
talking English,
so we must all help her.
Yes, Mommy.
First, I must say sorry,
I do not speak English very well.
You don't speak too badly.
You are very kind, Monsieur Pig.
But may I ask you a question
about talking English?
Of course. I'm an expert at talking.
Ask away.
Are English split-infinitives a form
of irregular verb or past-pronoun?
Uh...
Actually, it's quite late.
Shall we set up Delphine's bed?
Mommy, Mommy,
can Delphine sleep in my bed,
with a pillow at each end?
Good idea, Peppa.
[narrator] Peppa and Delphine are sleeping
at each end of the same bed.
[giggling]
Now children, try to go to sleep.
You've got a busy day tomorrow.
Delphine is visiting your playgroup.
Wow.
[speaks in French]
[narrator]
Dormez bien is French for sleep well.
I'm not sleepy at all.
Let's sing a little song
to make us sleepy.
Yes.
[singing in French]
[narrator] Delphine's pretty French song
has sent everyone to sleep.
Delphine has come
to visit Peppa's playgroup.
Madame Gazelle, this is my French friend,
Delphine Donkey.
[speaks in French]
Ah! Bonjour, Delphine.
Delphine sang a pretty French song
last night.
Can we teach her an English song?
How about the "Bing Bong" song?
Yes, sing me this "Bing Bong" song.
It would be good for my English.
Okay.
Ooh!
We're playing a tune
And we're singing a song
With a bing and bong and a bing
Bong bing boo, bing bong bing
Bing bong bingly bungly boo
Good. I have learnt lots
of new English words.
Bing, bong, bingly, bungly, boo.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator]
Mommy Pig is dressed as a fireman.
Mommy, why are you dressed like that?
I'm going
to the Mommies Fire Engine practice.
Ooh!
It's just a good excuse
for a cup of tea and a chat.
Well, what are you doing today,
Daddy Pig?
I've got a very important meeting
with the Daddies Football Team.
That's just a lot of grown-up boys
kicking a football around.
We're having a barbeque as well.
[door bell rings]
[narrator] Here are Mr. Bull, Mr. Rabbit,
Mr. Pony, and Mr. Zebra.
Is Daddy Pig coming out to play?
Come on.
Mommy, can we see the fire engine?
-Yes.
-Oh, goody.
[narrator]
This is Miss Rabbit's Fire Station.
Hello, Peppa and George.
Come and see the fire engine.
-Wow!
-Fire engine.
There's a ladder for climbing.
A hose for squirting water.
And a big bell, to ring.
Ding, dong, ding, dong.
Now, let's go up the tower
and look for fires.
-Hello, everyone.
-Hello, Peppa. Hello, George.
Who's for a nice cup of tea and a chat?
That sounds nice.
Ooh! A telephone.
Peppa, that is the fire phone.
It's only to be used when there's a fire.
[ringing]
Aah! Fire. Fire.
Fire station, where's the fire?
Where's the fire?
[Daddy Pig]
Can I speak to Mommy Pig, please?
Oh, it's Daddy Pig.
Daddy Pig, you're not supposed
to ring on this phone.
It's only for emergencies.
This is an emergency. I can't find
the tomato ketchup anywhere.
Daddy Pig, shall I light the barbeque now?
Yes, please, Mr. Rabbit.
Do be careful with the barbeque,
Daddy Pig.
Trust me, Mommy Pig, we daddies know
all about barbeques. Bye.
Maybe it needs more charcoal?
Give it a bit of a blow.
Put a few more firelighters on.
Now, we just have to wait for a fire.
How long do we have to wait?
Oh, it could be a long time.
I've been waiting ages.
How many fires
have you actually put out, Miss Rabbit?
Uh, none. Not one fire.
But you've got to be ready.
[ringing]
It's the fire phone.
Oh, can you answer it Peppa?
-It'll probably be your daddy again.
-Okay.
Hello. Fire Station.
-Hello, Peppa.
-Oh, Daddy. It is you.
You're very naughty.
This phone is for fires only.
Can you put Miss Rabbit on?
There's a good girl.
Daddy wants to speak to you.
Hello, Daddy Pig, this phone
is only to be used when there's a--
Fire.
[all] Fire. Fire. Fire.
[narrator] Oh, dear. Daddy Pig's barbeque
is on fire.
Fire. Fire.
Mommies to the rescue.
Whee!
Hold tight.
Fire. Fire. Ding dong. Ding dong.
[laughing]
It's Miss Rabbit's fire engine.
Hooray.
Stand back, Daddies.
Mommy Dog? Turn on the water.
Aye, aye, Mommy Pig.
[narrator] The fire is out.
Hooray!
-Thank you for saving us, Miss Rabbit.
-No problem.
It's all part of the service.
The Mummies Fire Engine Service.
And now that Miss Rabbit
has kindly flooded our garden,
we can all jump up and down
in muddy puddles.
Yes!
I love fire engines.
Especially when they make muddy puddles.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator]
It is bedtime for Peppa and George.
Good night, my little piggies.
[narrator] Granny and Grandpa Pig
have come for dinner.
-Hello.
Hello.
Where are Peppa and George?
They're asleep.
Oh, but I so wanted to see them.
Can I take a peek?
Okay, Granny Pig, but be very quiet.
[floor creaking]
-Granny Pig.
Hello, my little darlings.
You should be asleep.
Tell us a story.
Okay, but only if you promise
to go straight back to sleep.
We'll go to sleep after the story.
All right. Once upon a time there was--
A little boy called Pedro Pony,
he found a magic bean.
[Granny Pig] Oh, yes.
Now, Pedro planted that bean and it grew
into an enormous beanstalk
that went high into the sky.
That's right.
Pedro climbed to the top
of that beanstalk and found--
A horrible big giant.
But I don't want that. I want a princess.
Oh, yes, there he found
a beautiful Princess Peppa,
and Sir George, the brave knight.
[Peppa] And a cook who makes
the most delicious food ever.
[laughing]
[narrator] Mommy Pig, Daddy Pig
and Grandpa Pig are waiting to eat.
I'll go and see what's keeping Granny Pig.
What's next in the story?
Naughty Granny Pig.
You woke the little ones.
We promised to sleep
when the story ends, Grandpa.
I'm good at ending stories, Granny Pig.
You go down stairs, I won't be long.
There's a boy, a beanstalk,
a beautiful princess,
a brave knight
and a cook
who makes a lovely dinner.
Well, after they ate the lovely dinner,
everyone fell asleep. The end.
Then they all woke up
and along came a wizard.
A wizard?
[Peppa] Yes. A wizard. Who is going
to do a big magic show.
-But--
-Then, along came a scary dragon.
[laughs then roars]
[narrator] Granny Pig, Mommy Pig and
Daddy Pig are still waiting to eat dinner.
That bedtime story
doesn't seem to be working.
I'm the expert at telling bedtime stories.
I'll have them asleep in no time.
A scary dragon.
Peppa. George. Back to bed.
But Grandpa hasn't finished
the story yet, Daddy.
I'll finish the story.
I'll be down in a minute.
Okay, there's a boy,
a beanstalk, a castle,
a beautiful princess,
a brave knight, a cook,
a wizard and a scary dragon.
And a very hungry King.
So they all had a big dinner
and lived happily ever after.
The end.
Then they had a party.
And all their friends came.
[all laughing]
Right. I think I'd better sort this out.
[laughing]
-Daddy Pig.
-They're almost asleep.
Thank you. I'll take over now.
You have to finish the story, Mommy.
All right quickly now,
tell me what's happened?
Once upon a time, in olden days,
a long time ago...
Mommy Pig's been up there for a long time.
I can hear snoring.
At last. Peppa and George are asleep.
...and they all lived happily ever after.
The end.
Peppa. George.
Shush! Mommy is asleep.
[laughs]
It looks like Princess Peppa
is the best at telling bedtime stories.
That's right, I am.
[all laughing]